(All laugh and ссыл我覺得...)
Yes! So, um, it's a little late at night to shoot the opening.
Today is the day off for Kiracle. What are you doing?
What are you doing?
What are you doing? I've put together a video of our day off.
How was it? We're almost at the end.
Say it. Let's start the video.
Please start the video.
(laughs)
What's wrong?
What are you talking about?
So we're here for lunch.
What's for lunch today?
We have a lot to choose from.
Yes, sir.
Like this.
Pizza.
And Neapolitan.
I thought we could split it up.
Drink? Water?
Mm-hmm.
No, I'd like something to drink. Iced tea or orange.
I had iced tea again today. I could ask for it.
Lemon soup. Lemon soup?
It looks a little yellow today.
Is it the light? It's almost all outside light.
Natural light. But it's Golden Week today, so there are a lot of people. There are so many people.
I'd like to go out and take some pictures, but where?
I'd like to go out to take pictures, but where? It's windy.
It's already raining... I'm just pulling it out now.
It's going to stand out like a sore thumb. On the contrary.
People are seriously having lunch in tents and sheets. It's amazing.
Will this car fit? Can normal people ride in it? I don't think so.
Maybe if you pay for it, you can get in.
I came to the place where my friend works part-time today. Kira's friend.
I'll wait for her to come. Bye bye.
I delivered the food. I'd like to share it with Neapolitan.
Can I pour this on you? Sure.
Just a little.
Looks delicious.
We've been talking about Neapolitan lately. It's been a while.
I'm getting a little light-headed here. I wonder why it's different from before.
Bon appétit!
I haven't had pizza in a long time.
Long time no pizza.
I've been getting rattled lately.
The ship is moving.
It's moving pretty fast.
I wonder if it's like that one. It's delicious.
Cheese.
Is it good? Yes, it is.
Onigiri is delicious.
Put the meat on top of the rice ball.
Put onigiri on top of onigiri
It's the best!
Yugayakun ga
Indeed.
Lunch with a view of the sea.
Champion really work
It's an off day.
Let's go get this.
At my mom's.
Seriously, I've been going out to dinner with her and going to the gym... on my days off.
Yeah.
I wonder what you guys do on your days off.
You mean the other members? Yeah.
Yeah.
Today, you know, we're all off.
Yeah, we're all off today.
That's unusual. They're all off.
All eight of us off.
It's good, isn't it?
It tastes like old times.
I thought it tasted like cheese.
No way.
Wait a minute.
You have a different taste buds.
But isn't the Neapolitan more creamy like this?
No, the cream is more, like, tomato-y.
Did you have breakfast today?
I did.
What? What time did you eat?
Well, I woke up at 9:00 and had a fried egg, sausage and bread at about 10:00.
I ate more than I thought I would.
It's about 1:00 now.
Have you eaten?
It's 1:30.
I ate one piece of bread tonight.
I wasn't sure about it, but I was too hungry.
Did you ask me yesterday?
Did you have dinner last night?
Just hamburgers.
Yeah, Mom made it.
After the hamburger, I ate so much I was suddenly hungry.
I thought I wanted a cheese ball, so I went all the way to UBER and had a cheese ball, but I ate it.
I thought I was going to get really fat.
I want to eat cheeseballs on a regular basis.
No, I understand.
Cheese makes me want to eat it so bad today.
I love it.
Wasn't it on YouTube the other day?Wasn't there so much on YouTube the other day?
YouTube?
Yesterday's YouTube?
Yeah, which channel?
One thing.
A fan wrote something in the comments.
Something about Kira saying cheese again.
I don't remember, but a fan said...
Maybe I'm too natural.
What's your favorite food, Kira?
Beef tongue.
Beef tongue is delicious.
You haven't gone out to eat recently?
No, I haven't.
But even if we did, we've only been to Negishi.
Take me there.
Where?
You... Elle...
I think she's already been there.
But I was thinking of going on the 8th.
Why?
But she really likes beef tongue.
Yeah, it's strong.
Hey, I want to go. It's about time.
What are you doing?
It's some kind of water bike.
Oh, yeah.
I've done that.
I've seen it.
That's so much fun.
I've done that.
When I was really little.
Really? - Yeah.
It's a lot of fun. It requires a lot of speed.
It's definitely fun. You know that thing you can ride?
Like IH and titling.
Especially in foreign countries.
I want to go.
I want to go abroad.
I want to go to Ikwuame.
Ikwuame is a lot of fun, isn't it?
Do you have it?
No, I don't.
I wanted to go, so I looked it up, and it sounded like a lot of fun.
You're having fun.
You can make your dream of traveling abroad with friends come true.
That's great.
I think I can make it happen pretty soon.
I couldn't do that while I was still in school.
What do you mean?
I mean, financially, anyway.
I mean, it's not safe.
I'm just a kid.
After 20, you're free to go, right?
I'd love to go.
I've been waiting for you on YouTube one day.
On YouTube.
It's official.
Gual.
The best.
Good night
Good night, good night, good night, good night
Isn't it good
You found me to love me
There's nothing left to say
......
For the first time me and my element
My proof
Naturally.
I grew up.
You were a student, right?
Perhaps.
On any subject.
You.
battling
That's why
I said bye-bye
From now on
I'm going to go to the mall.
I'm going to go to a lot of shopping malls
I think I'm going to go there.
You got a lot of pictures of clothes.
Here you go.
Okay, I'm going.
It's good. It's good for YouTube.
The wind...
Wind.
Bye, bye, bye.
Wow! That's so funny!
Yes, so we said bye-bye a while ago in the evening, but we are eating dinner together again.
I am so happy.
After you go to bed, call me and let's go out for dinner.
Yes.
Moreover, we were just talking about the beef tongue at lunchtime, and I was in the restaurant.
I'm glad to hear that you were able to come before the monsters.
Me and my sister Shio.
Oh, it's Futago.
A-anashi and the video...
I'll make tamagokaji gohan.
Uma~Horse~!
I just told Mr. Queen
I'm going to eat this...
I didn't know there was such a thing as eating soy sauce
I don't know what that is, but I've got some soy sauce that I'll sell you.
I just put it on top.
Egg rice.
Oh, I spilled it.
Omelette and rice.
One person.
Laughs.
Yeah, yeah.
Funny story I did recently.
Funny things you've done lately?
Don't hit me.
I don't know.
I don't know, maybe recently.
No? Not recently.
I don't know. Talking is so hard.
I've given up.
I'm waiting.
What have we been doing lately?
Delibe.
And...
Rehearsals.
We're rehearsing songs we miss so much.
We're rehearsing again.
When can we show them off?
Please look forward to it.
Thank you very much.
I wonder if I can buy a black one.
Yes...
What shall we do?
I don't know.
Black is pretty strong.
I only got two.
I haven't had carrots in a while.
It's good.
You don't like it?
No, not at all.
Not at all.
It's good.
I couldn't eat it before.
But now I can.
Seriously.
Every year as I get older
I can eat more and more.
It's the opposite.
I want to eat the opposite.
Seriously?
Like...
Fruit.
What? Tronies?
Microfigure tronys.
Oh, I get it.
So they're doing killer trolls.
So you're doing Killer Toro, but on the other hand, you're getting younger.
Thank you very much.
A hundred yen.
A plate, a plate.
It's an intelligent size.
I'm too intelligent to eat it.
Why not?
Try it once.
Plate, plate, plate, please.
Are you finished?
Yes.
So, I hope you enjoyed the show.
Yes, how did you like it?
How was it?
It was fun.
Yes, we wore the same clothes.
We had a lot of fun.
Where are you looking?
I'm embarrassed to say I'm in the middle of the street.
I'm in the middle of the night.
Yes, they are looking at us a lot.
So that's our offer.
Thank you for watching today.
If you like this video, please give us a high rating, subscribe to our channel, and comment!
See you soon!